Guide to the Papers of Richard Phillips Feynman, 1933-1988
Archives
- Group II
  - Section XI: Supplements
    - Supplement 1996
      - Miscellaneous Publications
        - Megdal, Barry Bruce. "VLSI Computational Structures Applied to Fingerprint Image Analysis." Thesis, Caltech Computer Science Dept., 1983. (Box 92, Folder 8)
        - Lang, Charles Richard. "The Extension of Object-oriented Languages to a Homogeneous, Concurrent Architecture." Thesis, Caltech Computer Science Dept., 1982. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Supplement 1998
      - Course and lecture notes by Feynman and others, 1983, 1987-88, undated.
        - Notes and problems, "Drell-Yan Kinematics," partly in Feynman's, partly in another hand (undated) (Box 93, Folder 1)
        - Notes, unidentified, in Feynman's hand (undated) (Box 93, Folder 2)
        - Notes for Feynman's Physics 234b (Non-Perturbative QCD) 1983 (Box 93, Folder 3)
        - Notes for Feynman's Physics 234c (Non-Perturbative QCD) 1983 (Box 93, Folder 4)
        - Paper by P. Fisher with comments by Feynman, Physics 230a Fall 1987 (Box 93, Folder 5)
        - Notes for Feynman's Physics 230, 3 Nov-1 Dec, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 6)
        - Notes for Feynman's Physics 230, 5 Jan-2 Feb, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 7)
        - Notes to a Feynman course, unidentified (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Supplement 1999
      - Correspondence, RPF, Laurie Brown and others 1950-1951 (photocopies) (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Additional boxes:
      - Duplicates, including 3 v. of Lectures on Physics
      - Oversize box